What's New in Advanced SystemCare 13:

v13.0
+ New Email Protection protects your web emails against spam, phishing scam, and other email-borne threats.
+ Greatly enhanced Junk File Clean and Privacy Sweep to clean up more and deeper, and also clean up data for all user accounts.  
+ Rebuilt the database of Startup Optimization and Startup Manager to greatly speed up PC boot time.
+ Expanded the database of Spyware Removal and Real-Time Protector by up to 200% to remove more threats including the latest Worm.Mydoom, Ransom.FileCrypter, and Trojan.Symmi.
+ Enlarged the database of Software Updater to update 60% more programs.  
+ Significantly strengthened Privacy Shield to add protection for user-specified sensitive data.
+ New Context Menu Manager helps you manage context menu easily and quickly.  
+ Rebuilt File Shredder to newly support wiping free disk space.
+ Improved Registry Clean to remove more redundant registry entries for higher system performance.
+ Redesigned Turbo Boost to be easier to use and add optimization for Universal Windows Platform Apps.
+ Expanded the database of Surfing Protection & Ads Removal for a safer and ad-free online surfing experience.  
+ Revised UI for a more intuitive and fluent experience.
+ Localization: 34 languages.
+ And more can be discovered by you.